

# **MARCOS RODRÍGUEZ ORDIERES**

#### FRONTEND / FULL STACK DEVELOPER

Frontend Developer with involvement in Backend development and exceptional user experience, has diverse experiences as a background, including high performance, quality and responsive applications, websites, games and animations. Has a passion for developing and in the spare time, tries to learn a bit of everything.

# **Experience**

2019 - Now

#### FRONTEND DEVELOPER

ID League GmbH (2 years +), Berlin

Development of the KickID App for iOS and Android with React Native, the Web App and the Website in React, everything flavoured with Typescript, using the most up to date Features like Hooks, developing the necessary Components and writing unit tests with Jest. Involvement in the development of an API in NodeJS (Express + GraphQL).

2018 - 2019

#### FRONTEND / FULL STACK DEVELOPER

EasyOptimize GmbH - Shine (1 year+), Berlin

 Development of the Shine App for iOS and Android with React Native and the Shine Web Portal in React, implementation of Redux for state management and developing the necessary Components. Development of an API in NodeJS (Express + REST API + PostgreSQL).

2017 - 2018

#### **FULL STACK DEVELOPER INTERN**

Capgemini (1 year), Spain

 Development and improvement of a Web Application for Carrefour, using mostly Vanilla Javascript.

#### Skills

- HTML, CSS and Javascript.
- React, React Native, Redux, Flexbox, Typescript.
- NodeJS, MySQL and GraphQL and REST API.
- Jest.
- Webpack, Git, Kanban, Code Reviews...

### **Education**

Land Surveying and Digital Cartography Engineering: Universidad de Oviedo - 2007 -2010 - Spain.

Web Development Certificate - 2016 - Spain.

## **About me**

- Telephone: +34 680225665 or 01703202570
- <u>Email</u>: marcosordieres89@gmail.com
- LinkedIN
- Website (Portfolio)
- GitHub (Personal Projects)
- Google Play